[

](https://theitbros.com/)

 Search

[Home](https://theitbros.com/) Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

At **TheITBros.com**, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **https://theitbros.com**, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

### What type of personal data we are collecting?

1. We are collecting certain personal information about our visitors and users.
2. The most common types of the data we collecting are the things like: usernames, member names, email addresses, IP addresses, images, blog comments, and website’s analytics data.

### How do we collect personal data?

1. Our website collects personal data directly when you provide it to us, it happens automatically when you are navigating via the website.
2. We are collecting your personal data when you provide it to us: when you subscribe to a newsletter, email list, or send us a communication through contact form.

### Personal data we collect about you from other users

Although we generally collect personal information directly from you, on occasion, we also collect certain categories of personal information about you from other sources.

Third party service providers (like Google, Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, LinkedIn) who are located in the US, Canada, Ireland or UK, which may provide information about you when you link, connect, or login to your account with the third party provider and they send us information such as your registration and profile from that service. The information varies and is controlled by that service provider or as authorized by you via your privacy settings at that service provider.

### How we can use your personal data

1. We will use your personal data:
    1. Where this is necessary for purposes which are in our, or third parties, legitimate interests. These interests include:
        1. Managing relationships with you. For example, through responding to your comments or queries submitted to us using contact form on the website;
        2. Improving our website and content.
    2. Where you give us consent:
        1. We are noticing users about our privacy policy using a pop-up message, that appears on the screen. So when navigating content, closing the message or by pressing on **I got** **it** button on it, you agree with the terms mentioned in this Privacy Policy (like advertising that appears on the website – where this involves the use of cookies or similar technologies – in order to provide a more personalized experience).
    3. For purposes that required by law.
    4. For the purpose of responding to requests by government, a court of law, or law enforcement authorities conducting investigation.

### In what cases we disclose your personal information

1. We will disclose personal information to the following recipients:
    1. Subcontractors and service providers who assist us in connection with the ways we use personal information (as set out above), in particular: website hosting providers; third-party technical and customer support services; analytics services which are located in the US; subscription management services which are located in the US. In addition, our subcontractors and services providers may also transfer and access such data from other countries in which they are operating.
    2. Other recipients where we are authorized or required by law to do so.

### How we keep your personal information secure

We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by our service providers, and occasionally hard copy files that are kept in a secure location. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication, two-factor authentication, and data encryption where appropriate. It’s being stored on secure servers that are managed by our service providers, and occasionally hard copy files that are kept in a secure location.

### How user can access the personal data?

You can access the personal information that we collect about you by making a request to access other personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. In order to make request, contact us using the contact form on [Contact us](https://theitbros.com/contact-us/) page.

### Marketing Choices regarding your personal information

1. In case we have your consent to do so (e.g. if you have subscribed our e-mail lists or have indicated that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us using contact form), we send you marketing communications by email about new articles on the website that we feel may be a field of interest to you. You can always use a stop ‘opt-out’ of such communications if you would prefer not to receive them in the future by using the “unsubscribe” facility provided in the communication itself.
2. You also have choices about cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies some parts of the website may not work properly.

### Cookies and web analytics

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on **https://theitbros.com** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program ([Adsense terms](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) and list of Adsense Ad Providers) and Google Analytics) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart\_adserving.aspx](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/enterprise/)

### Information you make public or give to others

1. If you make your personal data available to other people, we can’t control or accept responsibility for the way they will use or manage that data. There are lots of ways that you can find yourself providing data to other people, like when you are posting a public message on a forum thread, share information using social media, or make a contact with another user (such as a third party Author) whether via our site or directly through email. Before making your information publicly available or giving your information to anyone else, think carefully. If giving information to another user via our sites, ask them how they will handle your information. If you’re sharing information via another website, check the privacy policy for that site to understand its information management practices as this privacy policy will not apply.

### How long we keep your personal information

1. We retain your personal data for as long as is necessary to provide the services to you and others, and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your personal data, you can request that we erase your personal information (you can do that via Contact form on the website).

### How you can access your personal data

1. You are also entitled to ask us to erase it, or restrict its processing. You also have rights to object to some processing that is based on our legitimate interests, such as profiling that we perform for the purposes of direct marketing, and, where we have asked for your consent to process your data, to withdraw this consent as more fully described below.
2. In case you have concerns that are not resolved – you also have the right to complain to data protection authorities. The relevant data protection authority will be the data protection authority of the country: (1) of your habitual residence; (2) of your place of work; or (3) in which you consider the alleged infringement has occurred.

Both personal information and personal data have the same meaning in the context of this Privacy Policy.

Share [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https://theitbros.com/privacy-policy/)[Twitter](https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article:%20Privacy%20Policy%20-%20https://theitbros.com/privacy-policy/)[Pinterest](https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftheitbros.com%2Fprivacy-policy%2F&description=Privacy+Policy)[Email](mailto:?subject=Privacy%20Policy&BODY=https://theitbros.com/privacy-policy/)[](#)

@2023 - TheITBros.com. Owned and operated by KARDASHEVSKIY K.B. FOP

### Shopping Cart

Close

No products in the cart.

Close
